This is crazy. So while everyone is obsessed with FIFA and the World Cup going on right now
So instead of watching it myself, I decided to make money from it and I'm just crushing it on YouTube right now
Now hear me out. You don't need to show your face on camera anymore to make money off of YouTube
You can use AI technology and do it faceless
And I'm about to show you how I make over $40,000 a month hopping on trends like these using AI
First you got to pick a niche. Obviously we already know the niche
We want to walk into which is FIFA, you know soccer or football depends on where you're from and they're getting millions of views
So we know it's a good niche walk into a niche that gets lots of views
That's the secret because views equals money
Okay, so first step head over to videdge.ai and they have everything we need to do this
So go to video ideas section once you do that right down either a video idea that you have in mind or you can click the button
Here's saying generate video ideas and it'll come up with ideas based on back to viral research for you
All right, so once that's done then you want to go ahead and click on the button saying create thumbnail now
Either you can have AI create for you in seconds or you can just make it yourself with AI
If you want to do more customization
We're gonna go ahead and click on auto generate for us to save time because I'm lazy today and just like that
We already got a thumbnail done. All right, so now what we do from this side is you scroll up
There's this little area saying done start writing scripts one button. We click on it
We say how long we want our script to be I'm gonna say three minutes make it short
Then I'm gonna go ahead and select auto pick so then that way the AI already knows what to create on writing style for me
Continue to write hook write hook and now it's gonna go ahead and start writing the entire script for me section by section
Okay, so now that the script is completely done for us all we gotta do is click this button up here
Saying done in turn script into voice over it will now send us over to the next step
Which is picking an AI narration to read off that script that we just wrote
I'm gonna go ahead and probably select this voice embrace the possibilities not bad
So we're gonna go ahead and click select voice then go to continue. All right
Then we're gonna go ahead and click the buttons and don and get AI to generate the video for us
And then what it's gonna do is gonna load up a little area that we have to fill out here
So there's gonna be a real-life footage video not animation video
I'm probably gonna select documentaries probably what it's gonna be click the button
This is generate and then we come back to this in about 10 maybe 20 minutes and the video should be edited for us
And just like that your video is completely done and
Every soccer expert who thinks that's impossible is missing three converging factors that make it inevitable
Now look sometimes I know it can be confusing to get started and make money online
That's why I create a free training if you want it just call it the word guy and I'll send it to you